[{"answer": "No.    Why should I", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, well... I hate strawberries", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, I'm pregnant, you fuck", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, pregnant", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, pregnant", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What do you mean, what the fuck did I get pregnant for? You got me fucking pregnant, you fuck", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hey, fuck you, you condescending prick", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Hey, fuck you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hey, fuck you", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hey, fuck you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I know what you mean", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I know what you mean", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Nice. You got suppresers with those, I'm assuming", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Glad to hear it.       Wasn't sure", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Por favor. No me mates, senor.   Tengo tres bebes. my friend sucks in a deep gulp of air. His hand shakes.   He pulls out Spans", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Que? my friend. Again", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Good for you. Listen, my friend. We've ended up with a damn hole in our daytime schedule. I've been reviewing some options, and it occurred to me there might be a place here for you and your baby", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The Dating Game.  That is your baby, isn't it, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "My baby, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes sir, it is", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "The Dating Game.  That is your baby, isn't it, my friend", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Are you still interested", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Look, my friend, nobody is indifferent to these shows. Right? And that's good. Show business must avoid indifference at all costs", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Taste is just a word", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm busy. We're in the middle of a bachelorette crisis out there", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You got any weed", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Ready one, take one. Ready three, take three. Ready one, take one", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Ready two, take two.   This guy has never been on a date", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I can't believe you asked me that", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I hate you so much right now", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It's a", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I got something for your head", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend, what do you suppose God thinks of someone like me", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes, God", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I can't quit? But I get panicky, my friend, in front of all those people", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I lack confidence", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "My God. Everyone you know kills themselves. Or tries. Who is it this time", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why'd he do it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I do not get stood up.   Do you understand", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Are you serious? That's what I do for a living", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Of course I do", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Pen", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You don't know the half of it", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " You know me as the creator of The Dating Game, The Newlywed Game, The Family Game, The Game Game, How's Your Mothe", "docId": "Confessions-of-a-Dangerous-Mind.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah, Operation Entertainment. The Ra", "qsentId": 46}]